<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE extension SYSTEM "langformat.dtd" [
  <!ENTITY call "&#xF000;">
  <!ENTITY defaultcall "&#xF001;">
  <!ENTITY zwsp "&#x200B;">
  <!ENTITY site "https://42.rockett.space/v6/">
]>

<extension id="english" site-link="&site;profile.html">
  <command id="profile" name="profile" alias="p">
    <parenthelpsection>Lets me keep track of your online presence and handles.</parenthelpsection>
    <description>
      This command is like a much expanded version of Discord's profile, allowing you to display things such as your online handles, birthday, game showcase, etc.
      Profiles are the same across all servers, but people can only see your profile if they share a server with you.

      [Patreon supporters](&site;patreon.html) are able to have more profile fields, as well as a special bio!

      You can use expanded markdown in profile fields, such as linking with `[Text](http://urlhere.com)`. Useful for linking to profiles.
    </description>
    <helpsection args="['@user']">
      Gets a user's profile. If no user is given, gets your own profile.
      If a user shares names with a subcommand, you can use `+profile get '@user'` instead.
    </helpsection>

    <documentation>
      This command is like a much expanded version of Discord's profile, allowing you to display things such as your online handles, birthday, game showcase, etc.
      Profiles are the same across all servers, but people can only see your profile if they share a server with you.

      [Patreon supporters](&site;patreon.html) are able to have more profile fields, as well as a special bio!

      You can use expanded markdown in profile fields, such as linking with `\[Text\]\(http://urlhere.com\)`. Useful for linking to profiles.
      Each field has a length limit of 255, and field labels have a length limit of 32.
      You can define 6 custom fields. Patreon supporters have access to 12 fields.

      Each game can now have an optional description, for example, instead of just "CS:GO", you could have "CS:GO, Distinguished Master Guardian" just to show off how cool you are.
      You can have up to 9 games in your showcase, supporters can have up to 12.

      You can set a custom note that is up to 80 characters long. Patreon supporters have access to a bio which can be up to 2000 characters long.

      Changed in v6:
       - Added pages to help sort details.
       - Games management is easier.
       - Added better games showcase.
       - Field limit raised to 12 for patreon supporters.
       - Game limit raised to 9 for all users, 12 for patreon supporters.
       - Field content can be longer now (255 chars up from 80)
       - Can skip interactive timezone selection if you know what your timezone is already.
       - Games can have additional context.
       - Patrons can add a custom banner image to their profile.
       - Removed `&defaultcall;profile make`. This was not viable to implement in the new framework.
       - Moved the supporter bio from info to here.
    </documentation>

    <output>
      <list id="month_labels">
        <line>January</line>
        <line>February</line>
        <line>March</line>
        <line>April</line>
        <line>May</line>
        <line>June</line>
        <line>July</line>
        <line>August</line>
        <line>September</line>
        <line>October</line>
        <line>November</line>
        <line>December</line>
      </list>
      <line id="date_format">{day} {month}</line>

    </output>

    <command id="get" name="get">
      <parenthelpsection args="['@user']">Gets a user's profile.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>Gets a user's profile, or your own if no user is given.</description>
      <helpsection args="['@user']">Gets a user's profile, or your own if no user is given.</helpsection>
      <documentation>
        Gets a user's profile. If no user is given, then your own profile is fetched.
        This command is left in as a compatibility option, since the "get" keyword is no longer required.
      </documentation>

      <output>
        <line id="not_found">This user has not set up a profile.</line>
        <line id="not_found_self">You currently do not have a profile set up. Use `&call;help profile` to find out what you can use to set up.</line>

        <line id="overview_page">Overview</line>
        <line id="field_page">Identity</line>
        <line id="game_page">Games</line>
        <line id="bio_page">Bio</line>

        <dict id="overview_headers">
          <entry name="timezone"><line>Timezone</line></entry>
          <entry name="birthday"><line>Birthday</line></entry>
        </dict>

        <line id="default_bio">
          This user has not set a bio, they can create one using `&call;profile bio 'content...'`
        </line>
      </output>
    </command>

    <command id="birthday" name="birthday">
      <parenthelpsection args="'dd-mm'">Sets your profile birthday.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Sets your profile birthday.
        If the date is not obvious, then you will be asked to disambiguate, e.g. 1-12 could be 1st Dec or 12th Jan.

        Valid date formats are `year-mm-dd` `mm-dd` `dd-mm`. `/` can be used in place of `-`.
        for quickest results, just use `0-mm-dd` since year is not considered at all.

        Your birthday is automagically added to the list in `&call;event`. It is also used in the `&call;solstice` countdown
      </description>
      <helpsection args="'date'">Sets your profile birthday.</helpsection>
      <documentation>
        Sets your profile birthday, as well as adding your birthday to the list of birthdays in `&defaultcall;event` on all your servers, and allowing you to use the `&defaultcall;solstice` command.

        Valid date formats are `year-mm-dd`, `mm-dd` or `dd-mm` (the `-` can be replaced with a `/`).
        If the date is ambiguous, such as 4-6, then 42 will ask you for either 4th June or 6th April. To avoid this, use the year month day format (year is disregarded, so you can put 0 there.)
      </documentation>

      <output>
        <line id="PARSE_not_enough_values">I could not read the date. Make sure it is in the format dd-mm, mm-dd, yyyy-mm-dd or 0-mm-dd</line>
        <line id="PARSE_cannot_cast_values">I could not read the date. Make sure the month and day numbers are actually numbers.</line>
        <line id="PARSE_invalid_date">I cannot cast this date into any kind of date system. Make sure mm is between 1 and 12, and dd is between 1 and 28-31 (depending on the month)</line>
        <line id="PARSE_timeout">Date disambiguation timed out.</line>

        <line id="disambiguate_contents">
          Please select one of these dates:
          1: {}.
          2: {}.
        </line>

        <line id="success">I have updated your profile birthday.</line>
      </output>

      <command id="clear" name="clear" alias="delete remove">
        <parenthelpsection>Clears your birthday.</parenthelpsection>
        <description>Clears your birthday</description>
        <documentation type="parent" />

        <output>

        </output>
      </command>
    </command>

    <command id="timezone" name="timezone">
      <parenthelpsection args="'region/city'">Sets your profile timezone.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Sets your profile timezone to either a UTC offset or a country code.

        Your timezone is used in `&call;now` where the most common timezones are shown, as well as in `&call;solstice` to work out when your midnight is.
      </description>
      <helpsection args="'region/city'">Sets your timezone to a city, e.g. Europe/London. This is case sensitive.</helpsection>
      <helpsection args="Etc/GMT'+|-hours'">
        Hours offset can be applied here but it will not respond to daylight savings time.
        For instance, CET (Central European Time) would be `Etc/GMT+1`, but to have daylight savings, you'd need to use `Europe/Paris`
      </helpsection>
      <documentation>
        Sets the timezone in your profile to a POSIX timezone name.
        These names are in the format "Region/City" (with proper capitalisation). Region is one of:

        |---|---|---|---|
        |Africa|America|Antarctica|Arctic|
        |Asia|Atlantic|Australia|Europe|
        |Indian|Mideast|Pacific||

        And City is most likely the capital city of your country or state (or a notable state in your region)
        For a full list of valid time zones, check out the [twiki page](https://twiki.org/cgi-bin/xtra/tzdatepick.html)

        If you set the region to "Etc", you can add "GMT", "GMT+hours" or "GMT-hours" to set a specific offset. However, timezones set like this will not be able to dynamically react to daylight savings time.
      </documentation>

      <output>
        <line id="invalid_timezone">
          I could not understand the timezone you gave me.
          Make sure the cases are correct and it is written exactly as shown on https://twiki.org/cgi-bin/xtra/tzdatepick.html
        </line>
        <line id="success">I have updated your profile timezone.</line>
      </output>

      <command id="interactive" name="interactive" alias="i">
        <parenthelpsection>Selects your timezone interactively.</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Starts an interactive timezone selector. Useful for if you don't know what timezone you are in and are being effected by daylight savings.

          Since the embeds here are very large, it is only available for use in DMs.
        </description>
        <documentation type="parent" />

        <output>
          <line id="nyi">
            This feature is currently not yet implemented.
            Here is how you can get a timezone definition yourself. First, visit this website:
            https://twiki.org/cgi-bin/xtra/tzdatepick.html
            And find your region (America, Europe, etc) and city, then click it
            You'll see a part that looks like "Europe/London" in big letters. That is the part you need to copy paste.
            Make sure you paste it as is.
          </line>
        </output>
      </command>

      <command id="clear" name="clear" alias="delete remove">
        <parenthelpsection>Removes your timezone</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Removes your timezone. Commands requiring it will either no longer aggregate you, or assume you are in UTC
        </description>
        <documentation type="parent" />

        <output>
          <line id="success">I have cleared your profile timezone.</line>
        </output>
      </command>
    </command>

    <command id="note" name="note">
      <parenthelpsection args="'text'">Sets a short note at the top of your profile.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Sets a short note or tag-line that will be displayed on the first page of your profile.
        This note can be 96 characters long.

        You *can't* use any markdown here, as all the markdown characters will be escaped. Your note is rendered as italics.
      </description>
      <helpsection args="'text'">Text is the new note you want to set.</helpsection>
      <documentation>
        Adds a small note to the top of the first page of your profile. This note can be up to 96 characters long.
        Any markdown in your note will be escaped (and the escapes counted against its length.)
        The note will be rendered in italics in your profile.
      </documentation>

      <output>
        <line id="too_long">Your note must be 96 characters or less including implicit markdown escapes.</line>
        <line id="success">I have updated your profile's note.</line>
      </output>

      <command id="clear" name="clear" alias="delete remove">
        <parenthelpsection>Clears your note</parenthelpsection>
        <description>Clears your profile's note.</description>
        <documentation type="parent" />

        <output>
          <line id="success">I have removed your profile note.</line>
        </output>
      </command>
    </command>

    <command id="game" name="game" alias="games">
      <parenthelpsection>Manages your profile's games.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Manages your profile's games showcase.
        You can have up to 9 games. [Patreon supporters](&site;patreon.html) can have up to 12.

        Each game title can be 32 characters long, and the fields can be 128.
      </description>
      <documentation>
        Your profile can show what games you play and if you want, can also act as a skill showcase.
        A game's title can be no longer than 32 characters.
        Each game has an optional 128 character content field, which you can use to display things such as your online rank, best achievements, game review/rating, a link to a profile/friend code or a funny highlight.

        You can have up to 9 games on your profile. [Patron supporters](&site;patreon.html) can have an additional 3 games, for a total of 12.
      </documentation>

      <output>
        <line id="no_subcommand">To find out how to manage your profile's games, use `&call;help profile game`</line>
        <line id="profile_empty">Your profile does not have any games. Use `&call;profile game add 'name' 'description'` to add one.</line>
        <line id="invalid_key">Your profile does not have a game with this name. Remember that names are case sensitive and you need quotes.</line>
      </output>

      <command id="add" name="add" alias="create insert">
        <parenthelpsection args="'name' ['content']">Adds a new game to your showcase.</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Adds a new game to your showcase as long as you have the required space for it.

          You can use extended markdown in the content, such as `[text](http://link.com)`
          Name must be 32 characters or less, and field can only be 128 characters including markdown.
        </description>
        <helpsection args="'name' ['content']">
          Name should be the name of your game
          Content can be additional context, such as your in-game rank.
        </helpsection>
        <documentation type="parent" />

        <output>
          <line id="full">
            You already have the maximum amount of games. Please remove some first before adding more.
            You can access 3 additional slots if you decide to support my developers! &site;patreon.html
          </line>
          <line id="full_patron">
            You already have the maximum amount of games. Please remove some first before adding more.
          </line>
          <line id="already_exists">You already have a game called {0}. Use `&call;profile game edit {0} 'content'` to update it.</line>
          <line id="too_long">The game's description must be less than 128 characters.</line>
          <line id="name_too_long">The game's name must be less than 32 characters.</line>
          <line id="success">I have added your new game.</line>
        </output>
      </command>

      <command id="remove" name="remove" alias="delete">
        <parenthelpsection>Interactively removes one of your games.</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Interactively removes one of your games.

          I'll show you what games you have, and you reply with the number you want me to delete.
        </description>
        <helpsection args="'name'">
          Or I can try and delete the name directly.
          Name is case sensitive and must be correct to work.
        </helpsection>
        <documentation type="parent" />

        <output>
          <line id="success">I have removed {} from your profile's games.</line>
        </output>
      </command>

      <command id="edit" name="edit" alias="update">
        <parenthelpsection>Interactively updates one of your games.</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Interactively updates one of your games. I can only change the content, not the name.

          I'll show you what games, you first tell me the number, and then afterwards, you can tell me what to change the content to.
        </description>
        <helpsection args="'name' 'content'">
          Or if you know the name, I can update it directly.
          The name has to be case correct to work.
        </helpsection>
        <documentation type="parent" />

        <output>
          <line id="wait_for_content">And what do you want to tell us about {}? (`{abort}` to cancel or `{nothing}` to clear)</line>
          <line id="wait_for_content_nothing">nothing</line>
          <line id="wait_for_content_timeout">Game update request timed out.</line>
          <line id="success">I have updated your description for {}.</line>
        </output>
      </command>

      <command id="clear" name="clear">
        <parenthelpsection>Removes all games from your profile</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Removes all the games from your profile and allows you to start again.
        </description>
        <documentation type="parent" />

        <output>
          <line id="REQUEST">Are you sure you want to remove all of your profile games?</line>
          <line id="success">I have cleared all of your profile games.</line>
        </output>
      </command>
    </command>

    <command id="field" name="field" alias="custom fields">
      <parenthelpsection>Manages your custom fields.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Manages the custom fields you have on your profile.
        You can have up to 6 custom fields. [Patreon supporters](&site;patreon.html) can have 12.

        Names can be up to 32 characters, and values can only be 256 characters including markdown.
      </description>
      <documentation>
        Manages your profiles custom fields. Fields are arbitrary key-value pairs.

        A field name is up to 32 characters long, and the value is up to 256 characters including markdown.
        These are useful for linking to your social media or gaming accounts, as you can embed the link into it, e.g. `\[@MyTwitterHandle\[\(https://twitter.com/mytwitterhandle\)`
        Fields can also be used as crude bio elements. There is no strict requirements on what they can be used for.

        You can have up to 6 fields. [Patreon Supporters](&site;patreon.html) can have an additional 6, for a total of 12.
      </documentation>

      <output>
        <line id="no_subcommand">To find out how to manage your profile's custom fields, use `&call;help profile field`</line>
        <line id="profile_empty">Your profile does not have any custom fields. Use `&call;profile field add 'name' 'description'` to add one.</line>
        <line id="invalid_key">Your profile does not have a field with this name. Remember that names are case sensitive and you need quotes.</line>
      </output>

      <command id="add" name="add" alias="create insert">
        <parenthelpsection args="'name' 'body'">Adds a new custom field.</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Adds a new custom field assuming you have space for one.
          You can have up to 6 custom fields. [Patreon supporters](&site;patreon.html) can have 12.

          You can use extended markdown in the content, such as `[text](http://link.com)`
          Name must be 32 characters or less, and field can only be 256 characters including markdown.
        </description>
        <helpsection args="'name' 'body'">Adds a new custom field.</helpsection>

        <output>
          <line id="full">
            You already have the maximum amount of custom fields. Please remove some first before adding more.
            You can access 6 additional slots if you decide to support my developers! &site;patreon.html
          </line>
          <line id="full_patron">
            You already have the maximum amount of custom fields. Please remove some first before adding more.
          </line>
          <line id="already_exists">You already have a custom field called {0}. Use `&call;profile field edit {0} 'content'` to update it.</line>
          <line id="too_long">The field content must be less than 255 characters.</line>
          <line id="name_too_long">The field name must be less than 32 characters.</line>
          <line id="success">I have added your new custom field.</line>
        </output>
      </command>

      <command id="remove" name="remove" alias="delete">
        <parenthelpsection>Interactively removes one of your custom fields.</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Interactively removes one of your custom fields.

          I'll show you what fields you have set, and you reply with the number you want me to delete.
        </description>
        <helpsection args="'name'">
          Or I can try and delete the name directly.
          Name is case sensitive and must be correct to work.
        </helpsection>

        <output>
          <line id="success">I have removed your profile's {}.</line>
        </output>
      </command>

      <command id="edit" name="edit" alias="update">
        <parenthelpsection>Interactively updates one of your custom fields.</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Interactively updates one of your fields. I can only change the content, not the name.

          I'll show you what fields, you first tell me the number, and then afterwards, you can tell me what to change the content to.
        </description>
        <helpsection args="'name' 'content'">
          Or if you know the name, I can update it directly.
          The name has to be case correct to work.
        </helpsection>

        <output>
          <line id="wait_for_content">And what do you want to tell us about {}? (`{abort}` to cancel`)</line>
          <line id="wait_for_content_nothing">nothing</line>
          <line id="wait_for_content_timeout">Field update request timed out.</line>
          <line id="success">I have updated your profile's {}.</line>
        </output>
      </command>

      <command id="clear" name="clear">
        <parenthelpsection>Removes all custom fields from your profile</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Removes all the custom fields from your profile and allows you to start again.
        </description>

        <output>
          <line id="REQUEST">Are you sure you want to remove all of your profile fields?</line>
          <line id="success">I have cleared all of your profile fields.</line>
        </output>
      </command>
    </command>

    <command id="banner" name="banner">
      <parenthelpsection args="'url'">Adds a custom banner image to your profile.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Adds a custom banner image to your profile that will be displayed on the first page.
        This is only available to [Patreon supporters](&site;patreon.html).
      </description>
      <helpsection args="'url'">Sets the custom banner image.</helpsection>

      <output>
        <line id="no_patreon">You need to be a [Patreon supporter](&site;patreon.html) in order to use this feature.</line>
        <line id="invalid_url">This is not a valid URL that I can embed.</line>
        <line id="too_long">The banner URL must be 128 characters or less.</line>
        <line id="success">I have set your profile bio. It will appear at the front of your profile as long as you are a supporter.</line>
      </output>

      <command id="clear" name="clear" alias="remove delete">
        <parenthelpsection>Removes the banner image</parenthelpsection>
        <description>Removes the banner image</description>
        <output>
          <line id="success">I have removed your profile's banner image.</line>
        </output>
      </command>
    </command>

    <command id="bio" name="bio">
      <parenthelpsection args="'content'">Adds a bio page to your profile</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        If you are a [Patreon supporter](&site;patreon.html), you can use this to add a bio to your profile.
        Your bio can be up to 2000 characters long and can include extended markdown, such as `[text](http://link.com)`
      </description>
      <helpsection args="'content'">Sets your profile bio. This overwrites your previous one.</helpsection>

      <output>
        <line id="no_patreon">You need to be a [Patreon supporter](&site;patreon.html) in order to use this feature.</line>
        <line id="too_long">Your bio must be less than 2000 cha--- hold on, how did you trigger this message? Surely you sent me a single message, which has to be less than 2000 characters, right?</line>
        <line id="success">I have set your profile's bio. It will appear at the back of your profile for as long as you are a supporter.</line>
      </output>

      <command id="paste" name="paste" alias="dump check post see put raw">
        <parenthelpsection>Shows the unformatted content of your bio for copy-pasting.</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Shows the raw content of your bio to make copying it easier.
          This does not work if your bio contains code blocks.
        </description>

        <output>

        </output>
      </command>

      <command id="clear" name="clear" alias="delete remove">
        <parenthelpsection>Clears your bio.</parenthelpsection>
        <description>
          Removes your profile bio content. Use `&call;profile bio paste` to get a copy paste version first.
        </description>

        <output>
          <line id="success">I have cleared your profile's bio.</line>
        </output>
      </command>
    </command>

    <command id="delete" name="delete" alias="remove destroy nuke">
      <parenthelpsection>Deletes your entire profile.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Deletes your entire profile, including timezone, birthday, custom fields and games.
        This action cannot be undone, so you'll have to set everything up again.
      </description>

      <output>
        <line id="request_1">
          Are you sure you want to delete your profile? This cannot be undone.
          Type `{confirm}` to delete, or `{abort}` to cancel.
        </line>
        <line id="request_2">
          Are you *really* sure? **This CANNOT be undone**, you'd have to redo everything again.
          Type `{confirm}` to delete, or `{abort}` to cancel.
        </line>
        <line id="success">I have deleted your profile.</line>
        <line id="timeout">Profile delete request timed out.</line>
      </output>
    </command>
  </command>

  <command id="event" name="event" alias="birthday birthdays calendar events">
    <parenthelpsection>Accesses my calendar</parenthelpsection>
    <description>
      This calendar tells you upcoming birthdays for members in your server.
      It also allows for custom events to manage things like tournaments or server special events.

      To add your birthday to the calendar, use `&call;profile birthday 'dd-mm'`
    </description>
    <helpsection>Shows the next month's worth of events.</helpsection>
    <helpsection args="month">Shows the given month's events. Month should be between 1 and 12.</helpsection>

    <output>
      <list id="month_labels">
        <line>January</line>
        <line>February</line>
        <line>March</line>
        <line>April</line>
        <line>May</line>
        <line>June</line>
        <line>July</line>
        <line>August</line>
        <line>September</line>
        <line>October</line>
        <line>November</line>
        <line>December</line>
      </list>
      <line id="date_format">{day} {month}</line>

      <line id="overflow">
        {}
        and {} more
      </line>
      <line id="overflow_oneline">{} and {} more</line>
      <line id="month_ARG_ERROR">Month should be a number between 1 and 12</line>

      <line id="PARSE_not_enough_values">I could not read the date. Make sure it is in the format dd-mm, mm-dd, yyyy-mm-dd or 0-mm-dd</line>
      <line id="PARSE_cannot_cast_values">I could not read the date. Make sure the month and day numbers are actually numbers.</line>
      <line id="PARSE_invalid_date">I cannot cast this date into any kind of date system. Make sure mm is between 1 and 12, and dd is between 1 and 28-31 (depending on the month)</line>
      <line id="PARSE_timeout">Date disambiguation timed out.</line>

      <line id="disambiguate_contents">
        Please select one of these dates:
        1: {}.
        2: {}.
      </line>

      <line id="no_results">
        There are no events or birthdays this month.
        To add an event, use `&call;event add 'dd-mm'`
        To add a birthday, the relevant user should do `&call;profile birthday 'dd-mm'`
      </line>
    </output>

    <command id="list" name="list" alias="all full">
      <parenthelpsection>Shows the full calendar </parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Shows all the dates with events on the calendar. It only shows up to 2 events per day though.
        Use `&call;event` to just get a specific month of events, or `&call;event get 'dd-mm'` to get single days.
      </description>
      <helpsection>Shows the full calendar</helpsection>

      <output>
        <line id="no_results">
          There are no events or birthdays on the server.
          To add an event, use `&call;event add 'dd-mm' 'Event content'`
          To add a birthday, the relevant user should do `&call;profile birthday 'dd-mm'`
        </line>
      </output>
    </command>

    <command id="get" name="get" alias="day">
      <parenthelpsection args="'dd-mm'">Shows all the events of a single date.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Shows all the events for a given date (if any events exist.)
        Useful for days with a lot of events on.
      </description>
      <helpsection args="'dd-mm'">Gets a single days events.</helpsection>
      <output>
        <line id="no_results">
          There are no events or birthdays on this day.
        </line>
      </output>
    </command>

    <command id="add" name="add" alias="create insert new">
      <parenthelpsection args="'dd-mm' 'content'">Adds a new event to the calendar.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Adds a new event to the calendar on the given date.
        If events already exist on that day, it does not get deleted.
      </description>
      <helpsection args="'dd-mm' 'content'">Adds a new event named 'content' to the date given.</helpsection>

      <output>
        <line id="success">I have added an event for that date.</line>
      </output>
    </command>

    <command id="set" name="set" alias="replace">
      <parenthelpsection args="'dd-mm' 'content'">Sets a date on the calendar to a single event.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Adds a new event to the calendar on the given date.
        If events already exist for that day, they will be deleted and replaced.
      </description>
      <helpsection args="'dd-mm' 'content'">Replaces the events on the date given with a new event named 'content'</helpsection>

      <output>
        <line id="success">I have set this as the day's only event.</line>
      </output>
    </command>

    <command id="delete" name="delete" alias="remove">
      <parenthelpsection args="'dd-mm'">Interactively removes an event from the calendar.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Removes an event from the calendar on the given date.
        If the date has multiple events, you'll be able to choose which one to remove.
      </description>
      <helpsection args="'dd-mm'">Interactively removes an event from the date given.</helpsection>

      <output>
        <line id="no_results">There are no events on that date.</line>
        <line id="success">I have removed that event.</line>
      </output>
    </command>

    <command id="clear" name="clear">
      <parenthelpsection args="'dd-mm'">Clears all events from the calendar day.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Removes all events from the calendar on the given date.
      </description>
      <helpsection args="'dd-mm'">Clears all events from the date given.</helpsection>

      <output>
        <line id="success">I have cleared the events from that date.</line>
      </output>
    </command>

    <command id="wipe" name="wipe" alias="deleteall removeall">
      <parenthelpsection>Completely clears the calendar.</parenthelpsection>
      <description>
        Removes all events from the calendar.
      </description>

      <output>
        <line id="REQUEST">
          You are about to delete all of the custom events in the server.
          Birthdays cannot be removed as they are profile entries not custom events.
          Is this okay?
        </line>
        <line id="success">I have removed the server's custom events.</line>
      </output>
    </command>
  </command>

  <command id="now" name="now" alias="time tz timezone">
    <parenthelpsection>Shows the timezones of server members.</parenthelpsection>
    <description>
      Shows the timezone of you, an optional target member, and the most common timezones on the server.
    </description>
    <helpsection args="['@target']">Gets the timezone of you and a target.</helpsection>

    <output>
      <line id="header">Set your timezone with `&call;profile timezone 'Region/City'`</line>
      <line id="42_time">My Timezone</line>
      <line id="user_time">{}'s Timezone</line>
      <pluralgroup id="sum_time">
        <plural value="1">1 Online Member</plural>
        <plural>{} Online Members</plural>
      </pluralgroup>
      <line id="time_format">{0:%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S}</line>
      <line id="utc_date">Time now: **{0:%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S}** UTC</line>
      <line id="snowflake">Maximum Discord ID: {}</line>
      <line id="footer">Your time</line>
    </output>
  </command>

</extension>
